Guide to the Duke University Progress Pictures Collection, 1925-1932
University Archives Duke University Durham, N.C., USA
- West Campus
  - 19280702WC0092.jpg (Image 248)
    - 1928-07-02
    - Showing Union Building taken from near the end of Group "C" Dormitories.
    - Union
  - 19280702WC0093.jpg (Image 249)
    - 1928-07-02
    - Showing foundation completed for School of Religion and forms built for concrete foundation for Library.
    - Divinity
  - 19280702WC0094.jpg (Image 250)
    - 1928-07-02
    - View showing Union Building, taken from near location of Chapel. In foreground to the right is location of classroom and Auditorium Building.
    - Union
  - 19280702WC0095.jpg (Image 251)
    - 1928-07-02
    - Showing forms built for concrete foundation for Library.
    - Library
  - 19280702WC0096.jpg (Image 252)
    - 1928-07-02
    - Heating Plant showing construction of coal trestle.
    - Heating plant
  - 19280702WC0097.jpg (Image 253)
    - 1928-07-02
    - Heating Plant showing masonry foundation completed, ready for steel superstructure.
    - Heating plant
  - 19280801WC0098.jpg (Image 254)
    - 1928-08-01
    - View showing service entrance to Hospital.
    - Hospital
  - 19280801WC0099.jpg (Image 255)
    - 1928-08-01
    - View showing steelwork on Hospital, also shows foundation for steel of Medical School.
    - Medicine
  - 19280801WC0100.jpg (Image 256)
    - 1928-08-01
    - View showing concrete foundation of School of Religion and Library completed ready for steel and stonework.
    - Divinity
  - 19280801WC0101.jpg (Image 257)
    - 1928-08-01
    - View showing Union Building, taken from location of Chapel. This shows stonework almost to second floor of Union Building. On right of picture is location of classroom and Auditorium Building.
    - Union
  - 19280801WC0102.jpg (Image 258)
    - 1928-08-01
    - View taken from center of Quadrangle showing front of Union Building. To the left of picture is shown Group "C" Dormitories.
    - Union
  - 19280801WC0103.jpg (Image 259)
    - 1928-08-01
    - View taken from Quadrangle near corner of Library showing concrete foundation of Library and foundation of School of Religion. At upper left is shown part of the Union Building.
    - Library
  - 19280801WC0104.jpg (Image 260)
    - 1928-08-01
    - View taken from end of Quadrangle showing part of Group "C" Dormitories.
    - Kilgo - C
  - 19280801WC0105.jpg (Image 261)
    - 1928-08-01
    - View showing Heating Plant.
    - Heating plant
  - 19280801WC0106.jpg (Image 262)
    - 1928-08-01
    - View showing Heating Plant. Practically all of structural steel is erected, including coal bunkers. Trestle in foreground for unloading and storing coal.
    - Heating plant
  - 19280901WC0107.jpg (Image 263)
    - 1928-09-01
    - View showing elevation of Hospital at service entrance.
    - Hospital
  - 19280901WC0108.jpg (Image 264)
    - 1928-09-01
    - View looking across foundation for Medical School showing Hospital.
    - Hospital
  - 19280901WC0109.jpg (Image 265)
    - 1928-09-01
    - View taken from near the location of Chapel looking across foundation for School of Religion and Library.
    - Divinity
  - 19280901WC0110.jpg (Image 266)
    - 1928-09-01
    - View taken from near the location of Chapel, looking across foundation for classroom and Auditorium, showing Union Building in the background.
    - Union
  - 19280901WC0111.jpg (Image 267)
    - 1928-09-01
    - View taken from main Quadrangle, looking across foundation of Library and School of Religion, showing location for Chapel in the upper left hand part of the picture.
    - Library
  - 19280901WC0112.jpg (Image 268)
    - 1928-09-01
    - View taken from near the center of the main Quadrangles showing Union Building.
    - Union
  - 19280901WC0113.jpg (Image 269)
    - 1928-09-01
    - View taken from the end of the Quadrangle showing the end of Group "C" Dormitories. This shows steelwork and stone completed ready for roof slab.
    - Kilgo - C
  - 19280901WC0114.jpg (Image 270)
    - 1928-09-01
    - View showing Heating Plant. All steelwork has been erected and brickwork started.
    - Heating plant
  - 19280901WC0115.jpg (Image 271)
    - 1928-09-01
    - Showing Heating Plant and foundation for stack.
    - Heating plant
  - 19281001WC0116.jpg (Image 272)
    - 1928-10-01
    - View showing elevation of wing of Hosptial at service court entrance.
    - Hospital
  - 19281001WC0117.jpg (Image 273)
    - 1928-10-01
    - View showing foundation for Medical School in foreground with Hospital in background. The steel roof on the Hospital except the upper left hand corner is completely erected.
    - Hospital
  - 19281001WC0118.jpg (Image 274)
    - 1928-10-01
    - View showing part of the first floor of Library completed and foundations for School of Religion complete practically to first floor level.
    - Library
  - 19281001WC0119.jpg (Image 275)
    - 1928-10-01
    - View taken from proposed location of Chapel looking across foundation for School of Religion and Library.
    - Divinity
  - 19281001WC0120.jpg (Image 276)
    - 1928-10-01
    - View taken from proposed location of Chapel, looking across foundation of Auditorium Building showing Union Building.
    - Union
  - 19281001WC0121.jpg (Image 277)
    - 1928-10-01
    - View taken from center of main Quadrangle showing Union Building.
    - Union
  - 19281001WC0122.jpg (Image 278)
    - 1928-10-01
    - View taken from main Quadrangle showing south and of Group "C" Dormitories. This shows stonework and steel complete ready for gypsum roof slabs. The two brick chimneys shown are complete.
    - Kilgo - C
  - 19281001WC0123.jpg (Image 279)
    - 1928-10-01
    - View showing Heating Plant with coal trestle completed and all steel erected. Brick stack shown in upper center of the picture.
    - Heating plant
  - 19281001WC0124.jpg (Image 280)
    - 1928-10-01
    - View showing first two boilers erected.
    - Heating plant
  - 19281001WC0125.jpg (Image 281)
    - 1928-10-01
    - View taken from the location of Group "B" Dormitory showing foundation excavation along Group "A" Dormitory.
    - Craven - A
    - excavation
  - 19281101WC0126.jpg (Image 282)
    - 1928-11-01
    - View showing elevation of Hospital at service entrance.
    - Hospital
  - 19281101WC0127.jpg (Image 283)
    - 1928-11-01
    - View taken from main Quadrangle showing structural steel for Medical School erected to fourth floor.
    - Medicine
  - 19281101WC0128.jpg (Image 284)
    - 1928-11-01
    - View showing foundation for Library and School of Religion.
    - Library
  - 19281101WC0129.jpg (Image 285)
    - 1928-11-01
    - View taken from main Quadrangle showing Union Building and Group "C" Dormitories.
    - Union
  - 19281101WC0130.jpg (Image 286)
    - 1928-11-01
    - View taken from main Quadrangle showing the end of Group "C" Dormitories next to Group "B" Dormitory.
    - Kilgo - C
  - 19281101WC0131.jpg (Image 287)
    - 1928-11-01
    - View taken from near Chapel location showing School of Religion and Library.
    - Divinity
  - 19281101WC0132.jpg (Image 288)
    - 1928-11-01
    - View taken from near Chapel location showing the foundation for the Auditorium Building and Union Building.
    - Union
  - 19281101WC0133.jpg (Image 289)
    - 1928-11-01
    - View showing Heating Plant.
    - Heating plant
  - 19281101WC0134.jpg (Image 290)
    - 1928-11-01
    - View showing Heating Plant.
    - Heating plant
  - 19281101WC0135.jpg (Image 291)
    - 1928-11-01
    - View taken from Quadrangle showing foundation for Group "A" Dormitory.
    - Craven - A
  - 19281101WC0136.jpg (Image 292)
    - 1928-11-01
    - View showing excavation for Stadium.
    - Stadium
  - 19281203WC0137.jpg (Image 293)
    - 1928-12-03
    - View showing wing of Hospital at the service court entrance, showing all stonework completed and scaffold removed.
    - Hospital
  - 19281203WC0138.jpg (Image 294)
    - 1928-12-03
    - View taken from main Quadrangle showing steel erected on end of Medical School. This shows stonework started on this part of the Building.
    - Medicine
  - 19281203WC0139.jpg (Image 295)
    - 1928-12-03
    - View taken from main Quadrangle showing Library stonework up to second floor. Union Building roof steel can be seen at the upper left hand corner of the picture.
    - Library
  - 19281203WC0140.jpg (Image 296)
    - 1928-12-03
    - View taken from center of Quadrangle showing Union Building. All stone practically completed on this Building and all steel except tower completed. Group "C" Dormitory shown at left of picture.
    - Union
  - 19281203WC0141.jpg (Image 297)
    - 1928-12-03
    - View showing Group "C" Dormitories, taken from Quadrangle.
    - Kilgo - C
  - 19281203WC0142.jpg (Image 298)
    - 1928-12-03
    - View taken from near Chapel location showing foundation for classroom and Auditorium Building and also showing Union Building.
    - Union
  - 19281203WC0143.jpg (Image 299)
    - 1928-12-03
    - View taken from near location of Chapel showing foundation for School of Religion up to first floor, and Library stonework up to second floor.
    - Divinity
  - 19281203WC0144.jpg (Image 300)
    - 1928-12-03
    - View showing Heating Plant.
    - Heating plant
  - 19281203WC0145.jpg (Image 301)
    - 1928-12-03
    - View taken from near Group "B" Dormitory showing concrete foundation completed for Group "A" Dormitory.
    - Craven - A
  - 19281203WC0146.jpg (Image 302)
    - 1928-12-03
    - Excavation for Stadium. This picture taken from top of the Players Entrance Tunnel looking south, showing grading on the left side of the Horseshoe very near completed. No excavation has been done on the right side of the Horseshoe.
    - Stadium
  - 19281203WC0147.jpg (Image 303)
    - 1928-12-03
    - View taken from the open end of the Horseshoe showing excavation of the East side.
    - Stadium
  - 19290107WC0148.jpg (Image 304)
    - 1929-01-07
    - View showing elevation of the Hospital at the service entrance.
    - Hospital
  - 19290107WC0149.jpg (Image 305)
    - 1929-01-07
    - View taken from main Quadrangle showing the front of the Medical School.
    - Medicine
  - 19290107WC0150.jpg (Image 306)
    - 1929-01-07
    - View taken from main Quadrangle showing Library Building, Union Building at extreme left of picture.
    - Library
  - 19290107WC0151.jpg (Image 307)
    - 1929-01-07
    - View taken from center of Quadrangle showing Union Building and Group "C" Dormitories.
    - Union
  - 19290107WC0152.jpg (Image 308)
    - 1929-01-07
    - View showing front of Group "C" Dormitories.
    - Kilgo - C
  - 19290107WC0153.jpg (Image 309)
    - 1929-01-07
    - View showing concrete foundation completed for Group "A" Dormitory. Medical School can be seen in upper left hand corner.
    - Craven - A
  - 19290107WC0154.jpg (Image 310)
    - 1929-01-07
    - View taken from near Chapel site showing foundation for Auditorium Building, also Union Building.
    - Union
  - 19290107WC0155.jpg (Image 311)
    - 1929-01-07
    - View taken from near Chapel site showing School of Religion and Library Building.
    - Divinity
  - 19290107WC0156.jpg (Image 312)
    - 1929-01-07
    - View showing Heating Plant.
    - Heating plant
  - 19290107WC0157.jpg (Image 313)
    - 1929-01-07
    - View showing grading for Stadium. Picture taken from center of Horseshoe.
    - Stadium
  - 19290107WC0158.jpg (Image 314)
    - 1929-01-07
    - View showing grading for Stadium. Picture taken from open end of Horseshoe.
    - Stadium
  - 19290109WC0159.jpg (Image 315)
    - 1929-01-09
    - Showing detail of roof on one end of Group "C" Dormitories.
    - Kilgo - C
  - 19290109WC0160.jpg (Image 316)
    - 1929-01-09
    - View showing Group "C" Dormitories.
    - Kilgo - C
  - 19290204WC0161.jpg (Image 317)
    - 1929-02-04
    - View showing front of Medical School.
    - Medicine
  - 19290204WC0162.jpg (Image 318)
    - 1929-02-04
    - View taken from Quadrangle showing foundation for Law School. Library and Union Building at the left.
    - Law
  - 19290204WC0163.jpg (Image 319)
    - 1929-02-04
    - View taken from Quadrangle showing Union Building and Group "C" Dormitories.
    - Union
  - 19290204WC0164.jpg (Image 320)
    - 1929-02-04
    - View showing wing of Group "C" Dormitories.
    - Kilgo - C
  - 19290204WC0165.jpg (Image 321)
    - 1929-02-04
    - View showing Group "C" Dormitories with foundation for Group "B" Dormitory in the foreground.
    - Kilgo - C
  - 19290204WC0166.jpg (Image 322)
    - 1929-02-04
    - View taken from Chapel location showing School of Religion and Library Building.
    - Divinity
  - 19290204WC0167.jpg (Image 323)
    - 1929-02-04
    - View taken from Chapel location showing Union Building and foundation for classroom and Auditorium Building at the right of the picture.
    - Union
  - 19290204WC0168.jpg (Image 324)
    - 1929-02-04
    - View taken from the rear of Group "A" Dormitory showing foundation for Group "A" Dormitory. Group "C" Dormitories and Union Building at the upper left of picture.
    - Craven - A
  - 19290204WC0169.jpg (Image 325)
    - 1929-02-04
    - View showing Heating Plant.
    - Heating plant
  - 19290204WC0170.jpg (Image 326)
    - 1929-02-04
    - View showing excavation for Stadium.
    - Stadium
  - 19290204WC0171.jpg (Image 327)
    - 1929-02-04
    - View showing excavation for Stadium, taken from open end of Horseshoe.
    - Stadium
  - 19290204WC0172.jpg (Image 328)
    - 1929-02-04
    - View showing site of Gymnasium, taken from point near Group "B" Dormitory looking toward Stadium.
    - Gym
  - 19290301WC0173.jpg (Image 329)
    - 1929-03-01
    - View showing front of the Medical School.
    - Medicine
  - 19290301WC0174.jpg (Image 330)
    - 1929-03-01
    - View showing the front of the Library. Union Building at left of picture.
    - Library
  - 19290301WC0175.jpg (Image 331)
    - 1929-03-01
    - View taken from center of Quadrangle showing Union Building and Group "C" Dormitories.
    - Union
  - 19290301WC0176.jpg (Image 332)
    - 1929-03-01
    - View taken from the rear of Group "A" Dormitory showing foundation for Group "A" Dormitory, with Union Building and Group "C" Dormitories in the background.
    - Craven - A
  - 19290301WC0177.jpg (Image 333)
    - 1929-03-01
    - View taken from rear of Group "B" Dormitory showing foundation for Group "B" Dormitory and showing Group "C" Dormitories. At extreme right center of the picture is shown part of the Medical School Building.
    - Kilgo - C
  - 19290301WC0178.jpg (Image 334)
    - 1929-03-01
    - View taken from near Chapel location showing foundation for classroom and Auditorium Building and also two sides of the Union Building.
    - Union
  - 19290301WC0179.jpg (Image 335)
    - 1929-03-01
    - View taken from near Chapel location showing School of Religion and Library Building.
    - Divinity
  - 19290301WC0180.jpg (Image 336)
    - 1929-03-01
    - View taken from center of Horseshoe at Stadium showing top of fills on each side completed.
    - Stadium
  - 19290301WC0181.jpg (Image 337)
    - 1929-03-01
    - View taken from open end of Horseshoe at Stadium showing top of fills completed.
    - Stadium
  - 19290301WC0182.jpg (Image 338)
    - 1929-03-01
    - View taken from rear of Group "B" Dormitory showing proposed site of the new Gymnasium. Stadium can be seen in the background through the woods.
    - Gym
  - 19290402WC0183.jpg (Image 339)
    - 1929-04-02
    - View showing the campus front of the Medical School.
    - Medicine
  - 19290402WC0184.jpg (Image 340)
    - 1929-04-02
    - View taken from campus showing Library Building in center of picture with Law Building on the right and Union Building on the left.
    - Library
  - 19290402WC0185.jpg (Image 341)
    - 1929-04-02
    - View showing campus front of Union Building.
    - Union
  - 19290402WC0186.jpg (Image 342)
    - 1929-04-02
    - View showing Group "C" Dormitories, taken from near center of Group "B" Dormitory.
    - Kilgo - C
  - 19290402WC0187.jpg (Image 343)
    - 1929-04-02
    - View showing foundation for Group "A" Dormitory, looking across Quadrangle showing Group "C" Dormitories and Union Building.
    - Craven - A
  - 19290402WC0188.jpg (Image 344)
    - 1929-04-02
    - View taken from Chapel location showing Union Building and foundation for Auditorium Building built to first floor level.
    - Union
  - 19290402WC0189.jpg (Image 345)
    - 1929-04-02
    - View taken from Chapel location showing School of Religion and Library Building.
    - Divinity
  - 19290402WC0190.jpg (Image 346)
    - 1929-04-02
    - View looking south, showing location for Gymnasium at road and Stadium beyond trees.
    - Gym
  - 19290402WC0191.jpg (Image 347)
    - 1929-04-02
    - View showing grading for Stadium, taken from closed end of horseshoe.
    - Stadium
  - 19290402WC0192.jpg (Image 348)
    - 1929-04-02
    - Grading for Stadium, taken from open end of Horseshoe.
    - Stadium
  - 19290503WC0193.jpg (Image 349)
    - 1929-05-03
    - View showing campus front of Medical School
    - Medicine
  - 19290503WC0194.jpg (Image 350)
    - 1929-05-03
    - View taken from main Quadrangle showing front of Library Building and part of Union Building at extreme left of picture.
    - Library
  - 19290503WC0195.jpg (Image 351)
    - 1929-05-03
    - View taken from near center of main Quadrangle showing Union Building tower
    - Union
  - 19290503WC0196.jpg (Image 352)
    - 1929-05-03
    - View taken from Chapel location, showing classroom and Auditorium Building, with Union Building at left.
    - Union
  - 19290503WC0197.jpg (Image 353)
    - 1929-05-03
    - View taken from near Chapel location, showing School of Education and Library.
    - Divinity
  - 19290503WC0198.jpg (Image 354)
    - 1929-05-03
    - View showing Group "C" Dormitories, with foundation for Group "B" Dormitory in foreground.
    - Craven - A
  - 19290503WC0199.jpg (Image 355)
    - 1929-05-03
    - View taken from the foundation of Group "B" Dormitory, showing Group "A" Dormitory. The Medical School can be seen in the upper left hand corner of picture.
    - Crowell - B
  - 19290503WC0200.jpg (Image 356)
    - 1929-05-03
    - View taken from open end of Horseshoe at Stadium, showing grading completed and concrete work started.
    - Stadium
  - 19290503WC0201.jpg (Image 357)
    - 1929-05-03
    - View showing the Stadium, taken from closed end of Horseshoe.
    - Stadium
  - 19290503WC0202.jpg (Image 358)
    - 1929-05-03
    - View showing location for Gymnasium.
    - Gym
  - 19290601WC0203.jpg (Image 359)
    - 1929-06-01
    - View of entrance to Medical School.
    - Medicine
  - 19290601WC0204.jpg (Image 360)
    - 1929-06-01
    - View taken from main Quadrangle showing front of Library Building and Law Building.
    - Law
  - 19290601WC0205.jpg (Image 361)
    - 1929-06-01
    - View taken from main Quadrangle showing the Union Building and Group "C" Dormitories at left of picture.
    - Union
  - 19290601WC0206.jpg (Image 362)
    - 1929-06-01
    - View taken from outside of Quadrangle showing Group "B" Dormitory in the foreground, with Group "C" Dormitories at left of picture.
    - Crowell - B
  - 19290601WC0207.jpg (Image 363)
    - 1929-06-01
    - View taken from outside of Quadrangle showing foundation of Group "B" Dormitory, with Group "A" Dormitory in the background.
    - Crowell - B
  - 19290601WC0208.jpg (Image 364)
    - 1929-06-01
    - View taken from location of Chapel showing School of Religion and Library Building.
    - Divinity
  - 19290601WC0209.jpg (Image 365)
    - 1929-06-01
    - View taken from Chapel location showing classroom and Auditorium Building and Union Building.
    - Page
  - 19290601WC0210.jpg (Image 366)
    - 1929-06-01
    - Stadium - View taken from open end of Stadium, showing playing field and walls around same.
    - Stadium
  - 19290601WC0211.jpg (Image 367)
    - 1929-06-01
    - Stadium - View taken from closed end of the horseshoe showing playing field and wall around same. On the left can be seen stepping for seat bank.
    - Stadium
  - 19290601WC0212.jpg (Image 368)
    - 1929-06-01
    - View showing concreting foundation for Gymnasium.
    - Gym
    - people
  - 19290608WC0213.jpg (Image 369)
    - 1929-06-08
    - View showing Stadium, taken from the southwest end of the horseshoe.
    - Stadium
  - 19290608WC0214.jpg (Image 370)
    - 1929-06-08
    - View showing the Stadium, taken from open end of horseshoe.
    - Stadium
  - 19290701WC0215.jpg (Image 371)
    - 1929-07-01
    - View showing front of the Medical School.
    - Medicine
  - 19290701WC0216.jpg (Image 372)
    - 1929-07-01
    - View showing the campus front of the Law Building and Library
    - Law
  - 19290701WC0217.jpg (Image 373)
    - 1929-07-01
    - View showing campus front of the Union Building, with Group "C" Dormitories at left and Auditorium at right of picture.
    - Union
  - 19290701WC0218.jpg (Image 374)
    - 1929-07-01
    - View taken from rear of Group "B" Dormitory showing Group "B" and Group "C" Dormitories.
    - Crowell - B
  - 19290701WC0219.jpg (Image 375)
    - 1929-07-01
    - View taken from rear of Group "B" Dormitory showing Group "A" and Group "B" Dormitories.
    - Crowell - B
  - 19290701WC0220.jpg (Image 376)
    - 1929-07-01
    - View taken from Chapel location showing School of Religion and Library Building.
    - Divinity
  - 19290701WC0221.jpg (Image 377)
    - 1929-07-01
    - View taken from near Chapel location showing Auditorium and Union Building.
    - Union
  - 19290701WC0222a.jpg (Image 378)
    - 1929-07-01
    - View showing Stadium.
    - Stadium
  - 19290701WC0222b.jpg (Image 379)
    - 1929-07-01
    - View showing Stadium.
    - Stadium
  - 19290701WC0223.jpg (Image 380)
    - 1929-07-01
    - View showing Stadium, taken from top of seats.
    - Stadium
  - 19290701WC0224.jpg (Image 381)
    - 1929-07-01
    - View showing foundation of Gymnasium Building.
    - Gym
  - 19290723WC0225.jpg (Image 382)
    - 1929-07-23
    - View taken from fountain location, looking along main entrance road toward Chapel.
    - Campus View
    - Along causeway towards site of Chapel
  - 19290723WC0226.jpg (Image 383)
    - 1929-07-23
    - View taken from intersection of main and Chapel axis, looking along entrance road toward fountain.
    - Campus View
    - Along causeway towards site of Chapel
  - 19290723WC0227.jpg (Image 384)
    - 1929-07-23
    - View taken from intersection of main and Chapel axis, looking toward Chapel site.
    - Campus View
    - main quad-Chapel Quad intersection
  - 19290723WC0228.jpg (Image 385)
    - 1929-07-23
    - View taken from Medical School showing Chemistry Building site. Law Building and Library in the center of the picture.
    - Law
  - 19290723WC0229.jpg (Image 386)
    - 1929-07-23
    - View taken from Medical School Building showing location of Botany and Zoology Building at left of picture and location of Chemistry Building where logs are piled at right hand edge of picture.
    - Academic
    - Academic quad from Davison
  - 19290723WC0230.jpg (Image 387)
    - 1929-07-23
    - View taken from road at the rear of the Auditorium, showing court between Union Building and Group "C" Dormitories.
    - Union
  - 19290723WC0231.jpg (Image 388)
    - 1929-07-23
    - View showing construction of the seat banks for the Stadium. At right of picture shows foundation excavated ready for concrete. Next - Steel form in place and men pouring concrete. Next - To the left, the finished wooden seats being placed on concrete. At the upper center of the picture, near the pole, shows location of guest box.
    - Stadium
  - 19290729WC0232.jpg (Image 389)
    - 1929-07-29
    - View showing front of Medical School facing Quadrangle.
    - Medicine
  - 19290729WC0233.jpg (Image 390)
    - 1929-07-29